=The Little Red Matchmaker= =Episode 18=
=الخاطبة الحمراء الصغيرة= =الحلقة 18=
Yingying.
ينغينغ.
The first milk cake in spring.
أول كعكة حليب في الربيع.
Shall we try it together?
هل يجب أن نحاول ذلك معًا؟
No.
لا.
This is bad.
هذا سيء.
Alas.
واحسرتاه.
Woody,
وودي،
no matter how many times I've practiced,
بغض النظر عن عدد المرات التي تدربت فيها،
I still feel uneasy.
ما زلت أشعر بعدم الارتياح.
Yes,
نعم،
I can cure a lot of intractable diseases,
يمكنني علاج الكثير من الأمراض المستعصية،
but now I'm just a lovesick fool.
ولكن الآن أنا مجرد أحمق مريض بالحب.
Blossoms are all open in my dreams.
الزهور كلها متفتحة في أحلامي.
Ripples of thrill pass through me.
موجات من التشويق تمر من خلالي.
The breeze understands my feelings.
النسيم يفهم مشاعري.
My mind is entwined with red strings of fate.
ذهني متشابك مع خيوط القدر الحمراء.
Well.
حسنًا.
It turns out professing my true feelings
اتضح الاعتراف بمشاعري الحقيقية
may take all my courage.
قد يأخذ كل شجاعتي
Woody,
وودي،
do you think I'm being too blunt?
هل تعتقد أنني صريح للغاية؟
Or maybe too hasty?
أو ربما متسرع جدا؟
Hey,
يا،
should I wait a bit more?
هل يجب أن أنتظر أكثر قليلاً؟
Let's try again.
لنجرب مجددا.
Yingying.
ينغينغ.
Master, were you looking for me?
سيدي هل كنت تبحث عني؟
Do you believe...
هل تصدق...
Tiantu acupoint.
نقطة الوخز تيانتو.
The glabella.
المقطبة.
Master.
يتقن.
Oh!
أوه!
Yingying,
ينغينغ،
memorize these acupoints.
احفظ نقاط الوخز هذه.
I will test you later.
سأختبرك لاحقا.
I
أنا
really
حقًا
like
يحب
you.
أنت.
(What a beautiful day)
(يا له من يوم جميل)
(for a love confession.)
(للاعتراف بالحب.)
(What a perfect day)
(يا له من يوم مثالي)
Yingying.
ينغينغ.
Master.
يتقن.
Master!
يتقن!
I forgot the medicine!
لقد نسيت الدواء!
You
أنت
and I.
و انا.
Make or break.
افعلها او انسحب.
Go for it!
أذهب خلفها !
Just say it.
فقط قلها.
Good luck.
حظ سعيد.
Master,
يتقن،
emergency!
طارئ!
Come on!
تعال!
Ma...
أماه...
Daniu?
دانيو؟
Hey!
يا!
I have a friend...
لدي صديق...
Go home already!
العودة إلى المنزل بالفعل!
Master,
يتقن،
actually...
في الحقيقة...
A man
رجل
should confess his love first.
يجب أن يعترف بحبه أولا.
Before I met you,
قبل ان اقابلك،
I was solitary
كنت وحيدا
and aloof.
وبعيدا.
I felt my world was pitch-black
شعرت أن عالمي كان أسودًا
without a trace of hope.
دون أثر للأمل.
But then one day,
ولكن بعد ذلك في أحد الأيام،
a ray of light entered my world.
شعاع من الضوء دخل عالمي.
It was your face,
لقد كان وجهك،
your smile,
ابتسامتك،
and your gentleness
ولطفك
that saved me.
الذي أنقذني.
I really wanted to take your hand back then
أردت حقًا أن أمسك يدك في ذلك الوقت
and have you lead me away.
وقد تقودني بعيدا.
But I was afraid to shatter the peace we had.
لكنني كنت خائفًا من تحطيم السلام الذي كان لدينا.
So I hesitated
لذلك ترددت
and held myself back.
وعقدت نفسي.
But I understand now.
لكنني أفهم الآن.
If you love someone, you have to say it out loud.
إذا كنت تحب شخصًا ما، عليك أن تقول ذلك بصوت عالٍ.
Yingying,
ينغينغ،
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
Yingying.
ينغينغ.
Let me help you with it.
دعني أساعدك في ذلك.
(So, was this hairpin meant for me all along?)
(فهل كان دبوس الشعر هذا مخصصًا لي طوال الوقت؟)
(Of course,)
(بالطبع،)
(dummy.)
(غبي.)
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I like you too.
أنامعجب بك أيضا.
♪On the battlefield of love, I'm a lone warrior covered with wounds♪
♪ في ساحة معركة الحب، أنا محارب وحيد مغطى بالجراح ♪
♪I've been through joys and sorrows on my own♪
♪ لقد مررت بأفراح وأحزان بمفردي ♪
♪How I wish you were here to grow old with me♪
♪ كم أتمنى لو كنت هنا لتكبر معي ♪
♪No matter the world's changes and absurdity♪
♪مهما تغيرات العالم وسخافاته♪
(To be continued) Changqing.
(يتبع) تشانغتشينغ.
Yes.
نعم.
You must save her.
يجب عليك إنقاذها.
If Yan hadn't suctioned out the venom,
إذا لم يقم يان بشفط السم،
I wouldn't have survived the snake bite.
لم أكن لأنجو من لدغة الثعبان.
♪As the moonlit night is drawing on♪
♪ مع اقتراب الليل المقمر ♪
♪A solitary wild goose is flying in the fog♪
♪ أوزة برية منفردة تطير في الضباب ♪
♪The waning moon is deep in thought♪
♪ القمر المتضائل عميق في التفكير ♪
♪Shedding a golden light over the road♪
♪ إلقاء ضوء ذهبي على الطريق ♪
♪I'm longing for returning home♪
♪ أنا مشتاق للعودة إلى المنزل ♪
♪I abandoned cultivation for a new life♪
♪ لقد تخليت عن الزراعة من أجل حياة جديدة ♪
♪And for the beauty in my heart♪
♪ وللجمال الذي في قلبي ♪
♪We meet only in dreams♪
♪نلتقي فقط في الأحلام♪
♪Souls entwine over the time♪
♪تتشابك الأرواح مع مرور الوقت♪
♪The shattered fate breaks the bond♪
♪ المصير المحطم يكسر الرابطة ♪
♪Years pass by like a dream♪
♪السنوات تمر كالحلم ♪
♪My yearning turns into a melody♪
♪يتحول شوقي إلى لحن♪
♪You are my eternal love in heart♪
♪أنت حبي الأبدي في القلب♪
♪My past life fades like clouds dispersing♪
♪ حياتي الماضية تتلاشى مثل تفرق السحب ♪
♪As I meet you in this life♪
♪ كما التقيت بك في هذه الحياة ♪
♪A thousand years of waiting is not in vain♪
♪ ألف سنة من الانتظار لم تذهب سدى ♪
♪Dreaming in a cool, long night♪
♪ أحلم في ليلة باردة طويلة ♪
♪Who is waiting alone♪
♪ من ينتظر وحده ♪
♪My endless yearning stretches on♪
♪ يمتد شوقي الذي لا نهاية له ♪
♪Despite the hard fate♪
♪ رغم المصير الصعب ♪
♪I hope to reconnect with you♪
♪أتمنى إعادة التواصل معك♪
♪And spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪ وأقضي بقية حياتي معك ♪